totalregistration.net 2019-12-17

# Total Registration Privacy Policy

**Last Revised:** July 23, 2019

Total Registration, LLC ("Total Registration", "TR", "we", or "us") respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you when you visit www.totalregistration.net or use our other products and services that include an authorized link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”), how we use the information we collect, with whom we share it, how we protect it, and the choices we offer you regarding our collection and use of such information. 

###  Students and Parents 

We work hard to provide test registration services to our school and educational customers. If you are a parent or student that is using our services in connection with an educational organization for test registration, then we process your information as a service to that organization and under its direction. To learn more about how your personal information may be processed and what additional rights you have regarding your personal information, please refer to your organization's privacy policy.

### Information We Collect 

We may collect personal information about you, meaning information that can uniquely identify you, from various sources, such as:

  * Directly from you when you use the Services, such as when you register for an account;
  * Your, or your student’s, school or other educational organization that uses the Services to manage test registration; 

The personal information we may collect about you may include, without limitation:

  * TR’s system requires first name, last name, email address, grade level and sex, exams, teachers, a password and security questions and answers.
  * Schools have the option to require more information from registrants if they desire.
  * Payment and financial details in order to process payments, such as credit/debit card number, billing address, cvv, and expiration date. Full credit/debit card numbers, cvv and expiration dates are transferred to the payment processor through an encrypted connection and are never stored in TR’s system.

When you use the Services, we may also collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag, or clear GIF, is used to transmit information about actions of the user opening the page or email containing the beacon back to a web server. Certain features of the Services may use local shared objects to collect and store information about your preferences and how you interact with the Services. We may also use third-party analytics tools (such as Google Analytics) that collect information about use of the Services and user traffic. The information we may collect by automated means may include, without limitation:

  * Information about the devices you use to access the Services (such as the IP address and the type of the device, operating system, and web browser);
  * Dates, times, and duration of use of the Services (including whether you are a repeat or first time visitor); 
  * Information on actions taken when using the Services (such as page views and website navigation patterns);

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information. It helps us to improve and personalize our Services, including by enabling us to identify and authenticate users.

### How We Respond to "Do Not Track Signals"

Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow the collection of information about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services. At this time, the Services do not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding such collection of your information, and the Services may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

### How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use information we obtain about you to:

  * Process registrations you place and complete other transactions you have requested using the Services, and provide you with products and services you request;
  * Send you information or materials you request;
  * Maintain a record of your registrations, purchases and other transactions using the Services
  * Respond to your questions and comments and provide customer support;
  * Communicate with you about our products, services, offers, and promotions;
  * Operate, evaluate, and improve our business and the products and services we offer;
  * Analyze trends and statistics regarding use of the Services and transactions conducted using the Services;
  * Protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims, and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users;
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards;

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

### Disclosure of Information ****

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction. We may disclose personal information about you:

  * To contractors and service providers we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request; 
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Total Registration, users of the Services, or others;

We also reserve the right to transfer your personal information to a buyer or other transferee in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale, or other transfer of some or all of our assets. Should such a sale, merger, or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use your personal information in a manner that is consistent with our Privacy Policy. 

### Data Security 

We have implemented measures intended to protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers behind firewalls. All connections are encrypted using SSL/TLS technology. Please note that the electronic transmission of information is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place to safeguard personal information will never be defeated or fail, or that such measures will always be sufficient or effective. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.

### Cookies

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features of the Services. 

### Accessing and Changing Your Information

You can review and change the personal information associated with your account by logging into your account and visiting your account profile page. 

### Your California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Services who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to info@Total Registration.net or write us at: Total Registration, LLC, 5013 Eldorado Springs Dr., Boulder, CO 80303

### Children Under the Age of 13 

The Services are not directed to, and Total Registration does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us at info@TotalRegistration.net

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Total Registration reserves the right to update or change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to our Privacy Policy, we will provide notice to you (by posting on our website) that our privacy practices have changed and will provide a link to the new policy. In the event we make a material change to how we use your personal information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date this Privacy Policy was last revised is at the top of this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for any updates or changes.

### Data Transfers

Total Registration is based in the State of Colorado in the United States. When we obtain information about you, we may transfer, process, and store such information outside of the country in which you reside, if you reside outside the United States. By using the Services, you consent to the transfer to and processing and storage of your information in countries outside of your country of residence, which may have different data protection laws than those in the country where you reside. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices, please call us at 800-974-2187, email us at [support@TotalRegistration.net](mailto:%20support@TotalRegistration.net), or write to us at:

Total Registration  
5013 Eldorado Springs Dr  
Boulder, CO 80303
